myweightlossdiary.info 2008-12-28

# Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy  
This is a privacy policy for our site who respects your privacy. Below is an outline of the information that this web site gathers, how it?s used, and how you can ?opt-out?

We invite you to contact us if you have questions about this policy.

You may contact us by filling out this form:

Contact Us

Site Visits:

Whenever you request a page through your browser, navigation and clickstream data such as:

    * your IP address,  
    * browser and version,  
    * operating system,  
    * date and time and  
    * the site from which you came

are stored in a log file and/or database.

When opting into our mail lists, your information is kept on a secure dedicated server hosted by Aweber.

The email addresses collected from opt-ins to our mailing lists are not sold, or disclosed to any third parties. These addresses will only be used by our business to send out communications (for example, newsletters). You will not receive any mailings you did not request. The email addresses collected at our web site are stored on a server hosted by Aweber. You can remove yourself from our list at any time by clicking on the unsubscribe link at the bottom of any emails sent from us.

When a contest/sweepstakes/survey is run on this site you may be asked to supply some personally identifying information like your name, email address and/or phone number by the third-pary company offering the contest/sweepstakes/survey. We are not affiliated with these companies and cannot extend our privacy policy to prevent these companies from using your information in the manner the deem suitable.  Please review the terms and conditions of any offers presented before you complete any of the offers.

Any data collected will be used by ourselves and our agents. olaysite.com hereby reserves the right to transfer any data collected in the event of an acquisition, full or partial, of the company or its assets.

If you have questions regarding our privacy policies, or require assistance in opting out of our email lists, please contact us.
